<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Superheros App</string>
    <string name="superhero_1">Izuku Midoriya</string>
    <string name="superhero_2">Katsuki Bakugo</string>
    <string name="superhero_3">Shoto Todoroki</string>
    <string name="superhero_4">Ochaco Uraraka</string>
    <string name="superhero_5">Tenya Ida</string>
    <string name="superhero_6">Eijiro Kirishima</string>
    <string name="superhero_7">Denki Kaminari</string>
    <string name="superhero_8">Momo Yaoyorozu</string>
    <string name="superhero_9">Yuga Aoyama</string>
    <string name="superhero_10">Fumikage Tokoyami</string>
    <string name="superhero_11">Mashirao Ojiro</string>
    <string name="superhero_12">Hanta Sero</string>
    <string name="superhero_13">Mirio Togata</string>
    <string name="superhero_14">Shota Aizawa</string>
    <string name="superhero_15">Present Mic</string>
    <string name="superhero_16">All Might</string>
    <string name="superhero_17">Endeavor</string>
    <string name="superhero_18">All For One</string>
    <string name="superhero_19">Tomura Shigaraki</string>
    <string name="superhero_20">Eri</string>
    <string name="superhero_21">Himiko Toga</string>
    <string name="superhero_22">Twice</string>
    <string name="superhero_23">Dabi</string>

    <string name="quirk_1">One For All</string>
    <string name="quirk_2">Explosion</string>
    <string name="quirk_3">Half-Cold Half-Hot</string>
    <string name="quirk_4">Zero Gravity</string>
    <string name="quirk_5">Engine</string>
    <string name="quirk_6">Hardening</string>
    <string name="quirk_7">Electrification</string>
    <string name="quirk_8">Creation</string>
    <string name="quirk_9">Navel Laser</string>
    <string name="quirk_10">Dark Shadow</string>
    <string name="quirk_11">Tail</string>
    <string name="quirk_12">Tape</string>
    <string name="quirk_13">Permeation</string>
    <string name="quirk_14">Erasure</string>
    <string name="quirk_15">Voice</string>
    <string name="quirk_16">One For All</string>
    <string name="quirk_17">Hellflame</string>
    <string name="quirk_18">All For One</string>
    <string name="quirk_19">Decay</string>
    <string name="quirk_20">Rewind</string>
    <string name="quirk_21">ShapeShifting</string>
    <string name="quirk_22">Cloning</string>
    <string name="quirk_23">Blueflame</string>
    
    <string name="description_1">
        Izuku was born without any unique superpower, or "Quirk",
        to call his own unlike his parents and 80% of the world\'s population.
        Despite this setback, he grew up with aspirations to be a hero in his own right and began to idolize the superhero All Might.
    </string>
    <string name="description_2">
        There was a time when Bakugo felt like nothing more than a run-of-the-mill rival who was there just to serve as a foil for
        the main character. However, viewers soon managed to see a deeper side to his character that peaked during his battle with Midoriya.
        Ever since then, Bakugo has managed to become one of the most alluring parts of the series,
        with his brash and explosive personality being an absolute treat to witness at times.
</string>
    <string name="description_3">
        Born with one of the most powerful Quirks in the series, Todoroki\'s character development and the acceptance of his fire powers
        have helped him become a standout figure in the series.
        While the latest seasons might not have placed him in the limelight as frequently as in earlier arcs,
        this is bound to change given his familial relations with Dabi.
        The clash between both heroes is going to make for a great time indeed, and fans can\'t wait to see this battle be animated in due time.
    </string>
    <string name="description_4">
        While Uraraka might not have had many instances in the series to let her Quirk shine, the character is still compelling to watch,
        regardless. It\'s clear that Uraraka is meant to be Midoriya\'s love interest,
        but the way in which their potential romance has been handled does negatively affect her character somewhat.
        However, players who manage to look past these occasional moments of poor writing will find themselves enjoying the personality of
        this bubbly character quite a bit.
        It helps that her power is fairly interesting and can be used in pretty unique ways over the course of the show — something that
        is very much required given that this character hasn\'t enjoyed nearly enough screen time in combat as some of the other side
        characters in the series.
    </string>
    <string name="description_5">
        The goody-two-shows of Class 1-A and one of Midoriya\'s closest friends, I
        da is one of the many characters in My Hero Academia whose Quirk holds quite a lot of potential.
        Unfortunately, aside from occasional moments such as his battle against the Hero Killer Stain,
        Ida hasn\'t really had the opportunity to showcase his skills in the anime.
        Hopefully, the later arcs of My Hero Academia will help him stand in the spotlight once again.
    </string>
    <string name="description_6">
        There was a time when many people thought Kirishima would be nothing more than just another hero in Class 1-A.
        However, it seems that his hardening power would prove to be quite useful during pivotal moments in the story.
        This led to Red Riot having his fair share of memorable moments scattered across the series, with his hardening
        Quirk proving to be quite useful indeed. Fans can\'t wait to see where else this fledgling hero will help out in the series.
    </string>
    <string name="description_7">
        At a glance, it didn\'t seem like Kaminari\'s electrical Quirk would be too much of a help since it ate away at his mental
        capacities in the process. However, just like everyone else in the show, he decided to work on his Quirk and improve its
        effectiveness in battle.
        This led to the hero performing some pretty cool feats, including the act of attracting electricity and preventing any harm
        from befalling his friends. It\'s only a glimpse of Kaminari\'s potential, which is sure to hit massive heights over time.
    </string>
    <string name="description_8">
        Some people may write off Momo as a character made solely for fanservice purposes,
        which takes on an added level of creepiness since she\'s still in school. However, despite her unnecessarily revealing outfit,
        Momo has proven herself to be pretty useful when the situation calls for it.
        She can conjure a ton of useful items and the like using her Creation Quirk. Without her help, Gigantomachia would\'ve gone on a
        rampage and destroyed pretty much everything and anything during the Paranormal Liberation War.
    </string>
    <string name="description_9">
        The idea of shooting a laser from a navel sounds like one of the stupidest powers around. However, in the hands of the right hero,
        this navel laser can be quite damaging and wreck most enemies with ease.
        Only time will tell before Yuga will show just how powerful his Quirk can be if he really puts his mind to it.
        His penchant for being flamboyantly hilarious really takes over his character at times, which is both a good and bad thing.
    </string>
    <string name="description_10">
        Operating under the hero name of Jet-Black Hero, Fumikage Tsukuyomi has one of the most interesting Quirks in My Hero Academia.
        The Dark Shadow is a sentient monster that, as its name suggests, grows more powerful in the absence of light.
        However, the stronger Dark Shadow gets, the harder it is for Fumikage to control it.
        Fumikage tends to slip into the background in most social situations, particularly early on in the story; however,
        this does begin to change as the anime progresses. Fumikage is powerful, well-liked, and reliable.
    </string>
    <string name="description_11">
        Given the large number of students in Class 1-A, it\'s only a given that not all of them will have a hugely prominent role.
        After all, even given the nature of anime itself, it\'s really hard to believe that every member of this class is spectacular and
        important in any way. This led to some characters not really being all that important in the grand scheme of things,
        and Mashirao Ojiro is a great example of this.
        His powers are pretty basic and nothing to write home about, making him one of the most unremarkable members of the class.
        Sure, he may be good in close-range combat and his tail gives him an extra opportunity to attack people,
        but that\'s nothing compared to the many unique powers that his classmates have.
    </string>
    <string name="description_12">
        The members of Class 1-A are meant to be prodigies with incredible Quirks that can help them become some of the greatest heroes
        of all time. For the most part, the majority of the students in this class definitely live up to this promise and do a great job
        of justifying their position in the class, but there are some heroes with powers so unremarkable that their placement in this class
        seems rather hard to believe.
        A great example of this is Hanta Sero, a student with one of the worst powers in the series. He can generate tape from his body,
        which may be a rather convenient power to have if someone needs to seal a box… but it doesn\'t really seem all that
        helpful during combat. For what it\'s worth, the show has tried to make him look pretty effective in combat, but there\'s a reason
        why he hasn\'t played a major role in some of the more high-stakes battles in the series.
    </string>
    <string name="description_13">
        Regarded as the top student at U.A. High School, Mirio\'s energetic and carefree demeanor doesn\'t give away just how capable
        of a hero and fighter he is. Prior to All Might discovering Deku, Mirio looked set to inherit One For All and become the new Symbol
        of Peace, and it isn\'t difficult to see why he was considered a worthy successor to this world\'s greatest hero.
        Mirio\'s Quirk, Permeation, turns him intangible, an ability that the student has explored to its full potential.
        While he might\'ve lost his powers during his fight with Overhaul, fans were elated to see him make a comeback during the
        closing stages of the Paranormal Liberation War arc.
    </string>
    <string name="description_14">
        The homeroom teacher of Class 1-A is a powerful hero. Aizawa\'s ability to cancel out Quirks for a limited period of time has
        proven to be quite useful in a tough spot.
        This, coupled with this knack for hand-to-hand combat, makes it easy to see why Eraserhead is a favorite of many fans.
        Given how events in the manga have developed up to now, one can only wait and see how he handles himself in a fight where
        everything is on the line.
    </string>
    <string name="description_15">
        Present Mic is a hero who seemed like nothing more than comic relief early on in the series. However,
        after his background with Aizawa is expanded upon, viewers realize just how important this character\'s backstory really is.
        This has made him one of the more intriguing characters in the series. While their third friend may be too far gone right now,
        fans can only hope that the friendship of this trio is rekindled once again.
    </string>
    <string name="description_16">
        The former No. 1 Hero is one of My Hero Academia\'s most recognizable characters, with his dual personality being quite
        intriguing to witness in its own right. However, while the current version of All Might may not be all that spectacular,
        his legacy more than speaks for himself and his achievements.
        A gifted wielder of One for All who managed to use this power to great effect in order to take care of any threats that
        would endanger the lives of civilians, All Might was very much worthy of the No. 1 spot in his heyday.
        One can only wait and see the role that his powerless counterpart will play in the events to come.
    </string>
    <string name="description_17">
        At the start of the series, Endeavor genuinely seemed like a horrible father. It was hinted that he\'d abused his wife and children,
        while he also seemed rather petty for being stuck in All Might\'s shadow until the forced retirement of the former No. 1 Hero.
        However, over time, Endeavor\'s character has been built upon quite a bit in order to humanize him more in the eyes of
        audiences who\'d only seen his savage side. His fight against the advanced Nomu was easily one of the major highlights of this character,
        and the fact that Dabi was actually his long-lost son has added a ton of depth to a character who seemed rather one-note at times.
    </string>
    <string name="description_18">
        A dastardly villain whose fight with All Might put the wielder of One for All out of business for good,
        All for One is an intriguing villain. Aside from the amazing fight that he has with All Might,
        his sporadic appearances throughout the series have also been quite entertaining in their own right.
        However, given how the events of the anime and manga have unfolded, it\'s very clear that All for One has no
        intentions of being succeeded by anyone else. The fact that he\'s trying to take over Shigaraki\'s body is proof enough.
    </string>
    <string name="description_19">
        Shigaraki is one of the scariest villains in the series. His twisted motives and horrifying power have established him as a
        compelling villain who is bound to play a major role throughout My Hero Academia.
        Shigaraki\'s dynamic with Midoriya has made for an enthralling watch. Most fans can\'t wait to see the personifications of
        good and evil in the series duke it out in the show once and for all.
    </string>
    <string name="description_20">
        Central to the Shie Hassaikai Arc, Eri is a young girl who has been through hell for most of her life.
        Eri\'s Quirk, Rewind, allows her to return a person to a previous state, which includes before they came to be. Eventually,
        Eri fell into the hands of Kai Chisaki, who manipulated the girl to his own ends.
        Eri is an easy character to root for. She goes through quite an arc in My Hero Academia,
        one that comes with an emotional payoff. Fans can\'t wait for the time when she finally learns to control her Quirk
        and becomes one of the most powerful heroes in My Hero Academia since she definitely has that potential.
    </string>
    <string name="description_21">
        Himiko Toga is one of the most captivating villains in My Hero Academia. Her yandere personality was an instant hit with fans
        who loved seeing this bloodthirsty villain in action. It helps that the unhealthy infatuation she has with Midoriya makes her
        even more riveting as well!
        The latest season of My Hero Academia took a deeper look at the villains and the lengths they\'ll go to ensure that
        Shigaraki\'s dream becomes a reality. This led to Himiko getting a boost to her powers, letting her imitate the Quirk of the
        person she\'s impersonating. Suffice it to say, it\'s clear that Toga will play a major role over the course of My Hero Academia
        and use her powers to great effect in later arcs.
    </string>
    <string name="description_22">
        Another villain who has become a fan favorite is Twice. The episode that expanded on his character was pretty interesting and
        showed a side of this villain that gave his personality some serious depth. The fact that he is conflicted about whether
        he\'s a clone or real is a pretty unique direction to take for this character, and his Quirk ended up becoming all the more
        impressive during the last season.
        After seeing Himiko almost lose her life at the hands of Re-Destro\'s lackeys, Twice unlocked a new power that let him make as
        many clones as he wanted without too many limitations. It\'s easy to see why this power would pose a major threat to the heroes,
        and only time will tell how Twice will make the most of his upgraded powers in the anime.
    </string>
    <string name="description_23">
        Dabi was already a pretty interesting character as is, with many fans wondering just how hot his flames could be.
        However, this was far from the biggest revelation surrounding his character,
        with this villain proudly revealing himself to be Endeavor\'s son, Toya Todoroki.
        It\'s clear that Dabi is bound to play a huge role in the coming events of My Hero Academia.
        His battles with his brother and son are going to be quite fun to behold in My Hero Academia,
        and fans can\'t wait to see this confrontation later on in the series.
    </string>


</resources>